San Francisco, CA

**408-387-2633** 

dmehrkish91@gmail.com

www.dorna.design

# **Summary**

Dedicated and experienced Product Designer drawn towards the technical aspects of executing a project. I'm passionate about creating simple, elegant solutions for complex design problems. My work is rooted in a deep understanding of end-users while still balancing internal goals & KPIs.

## Skillset

- Front-End Development
- Usability Testing
- User Research
- Content Strategy
- Journey Mapping
- User Personas
- User Flows
- Wireframing
- Hi-fidelity mockups
- Rapid Protoyping
- Information architecture modeling

#### **Tools**

- Sketch
- Adobe CC
- Framer
- InvisionApp
- Balsamiq
- HTML, CSS
- Javascript/jQuery
- Principle
- Github
- Zeplin

## **Experience**

Sept 2017 - Present

### Sapling, Product Designer

- Lead iterative product design in an agile environment including sketches, user flows, product requirement writing, prototyping and creating Sapling's first design system.
- Lead Sapling's user research process, which includes customer interviews, usability testing and a redesign of Sapling's personas
- Closely collaborate with product and marketing to create assets and a styleguide for Sapling's new website

Oct 2016 - July 2017

Bloc, Design & Front- End Apprenticeship

- Developed deep knowledge of agile design processes and tools in a full-time project-based Mentorship program with a seasoned designer
- Produced 4 end-to-end projects designed around specific researched personas with user flows, wire frames, & mockups
- Wrote and deployed functional front-end applications
- Presented projects to the Bloc Program Director in formal reviews

Dec 2015 - March 2017 Helpshift, Customer Success Manager

- Owned a client portfolio of mobile gaming and e-commerce customers; sustained MRR growth of 8% on average
- Managed all product training initiatives and materials including webinars, newsletters and knowledge base content
- Acted as a liaison between Sales and Product to create product implementation roadmaps specific to customer acquisition and growth; was able to prove a 20% drop in customer support volume due to improved internal collaboration

Oct 2013 - Dec 2015

Lyft, Voice of Customer Specialist

- Led CRM migration project and redesigned help center; used page view and email deflection data to measure success
- Improve team retention rates by 25% by revamping training and onboarding methods for the 700 person support team
- Launched a live chat channel for a new Lost and Found feature, work was featured in Forbes magazine

# **Other Projects**

 Ayande Company: Co-founded a group that aims to use dance to bridge the gap between Iranian and American communites. Created our brand identity and designed our website.

## **Education**

Aug 2009 - May 2013

San Francisco State University

B.S, International Business